Guide to the Records of National Conference on Soviet Jewry, undated, 1949, 1954, 1956, 1958-1993 *I-181 and *I-181A
American Jewish Historical Society, Newton Centre, MA and New York, NY
- Part 2, Series VII: Soviet Refuseniks and Prisoners of Conscience Legal Petitions, Affidavits and Memoranda, undated, 1971-1990; Boxes 154-161.
  - Subseries A: Legal petitions on individual cases by Telford Taylor, undated, 1974-1975, 1978-1979; Boxes 154-155.
    - Kaminsky, Lassal, undated, 1974 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Knokh, Leib, 1974 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Korenblit, Mikhail, undated, 1974 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Kuznetsov, Eduard Samvilovich, 1974 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Liubarsky, Lazar Moiseyevich, 1975 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Markman, Vladimir, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Mendelevich, Joseph, undated, 1974, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Meshener, Josif, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Murzhenko, Alexei Grigoryevich, 1974, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Penson, Boris Solomonovich, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Pinkhasov, Pinkhas, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Shkolnik, Isaac, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Vudka, Yuri, undated, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Yagman, Lev, undated, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Zalmanson, Israil Iosifovich, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Zalmanson, Silva, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Zalmanson, Vulf, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: Information on trials and sentencing of refuseniks and POC, undated, 1971-1975; Box 156.
    - Affidavits and Declarations, 1974-1975 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence between Telford Taylor and Roman Rudenko, 1974-1975 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Legal Memoranda I and II, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Legal Memoranda III and IV, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Telford Taylor Press Release, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Trials -- Azernikov, undated, 1971, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Trials -- Brind, 1972-1973 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Trials -- Feldman, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Trials -- Kaufman, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Trials -- Kukui, undated, 1971 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Trials -- Liubarsky, undated, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Trials -- Markman, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Trials -- Riazan, undated, 1973-1974 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Trials -- Shkolnik, undated, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Trials -- Trakhtenberg, Emilia, 1971 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Trials -- Zabelishensky, Leonid, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Materials for campaigning on behalf of individual Refuseniks, undated, 1972-1990; Boxes 157-159.
    - Articles on Anatoly Sharansky, 1977 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Articles on Anatoly Sharansky, January 1978-June 1978 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Anatoly Sharansky with Poster (see also OS1 folder, item I-181A.013), July 1978-December 1978 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Anatoly Sharansky, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Articles on Anatoly Sharansky, undated, 1980-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel, 1972-1978 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel, Janaury 1979-July 1979 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel, August 1979-December 1979 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel, 1980 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel with Photo, 1981-February 1982 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel, March 1982-June 1982 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel, July 1982-1984 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel, undated (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel -- International Day of Activity, July 20, 1982 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel -- Press Clippings and News Bulletins, 1974-1978 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel -- Press Clippings and News Bulletins, 1979 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Campaign to Free Ida Nudel -- Press Clippings and News Bulletins, undated, 1980-1984 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Materials for Petitions on Behalf of Prisoners of Conscience, undated, 1974 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Raiz, Karmella, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Shinbaum, Myrna -- Petitions of Individual Refuseniks, 1972, 1979-1981 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Shinbaum, Myrna -- Petitions of Individual Refuseniks, 1982-1988 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Shinbaum, Myrna -- Petitions of Soviet Jews, 1975-1978 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Shinbaum, Myrna -- Refusenik Profiles, undated (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Tufeld, Igor, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Subseries D: Lawyers' Committee Materials, undated, 1974-1990; Boxes 160-161.
    - American Bar Association, 1987-1988 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - American Bar Association and Association of Soviet Lawyers Exchange, 1986 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - American Bar Association and Association of Soviet Lawyers Seminars, 1986-1988 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - American Bar Association and Association of Soviet Lawyers Symposium in Moscow, 1986-1988 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - American Bar Association: California Branch, 1978-1987 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - American Bar Association: White and Case Secrecy Report "Who May Leave", 1987 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Contacts of American and Soviet Lawyers, 1985-1987 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - District Attorneys Delegation to the USSR, 1978-1979 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - District Attorneys Task Force on Soviet Jews and the Law, 1982-1984 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Greater Boston Lawyers Committee for Soviet Jewry, 1979 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Lawyers in Chicago, IL, 1979, 1981 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Lawyers in Cleveland, OH, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Lawyers in Philadelphia, PA, 1979 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Lawyers Travel, 1980, 1982, 1985 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Coalition for Soviet Jewry, California, 1979, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles Committee of Concerned Lawyers for Soviet Jews, 1985, 1987-1990 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Meeting of American and Soviet Lawyers, 1986-1987 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - National District Attorney Association, 1982-1983 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Lawyers Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - National Lawyers Committee for Soviet Jewry and International Human Rights, 1979-1983 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - National Lawyers Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - National Lawyers Committee for Soviet Jewry and International Human Rights, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - New York Legal Coalition for Soviet Jewry, 1979 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Refusenik Legal Representation Proposal, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Second International Legal Colloquium, undated, 1976, 1978-1980 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Sixth and Seventh International Congresses of Jewish Lawyers and Jurists, 1984, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 18)
    - Telford Taylor Project Fund, 1977-1980 (Box 161, Folder 19)
- Part 2, Series VIII: USSR Jewish Émigrés Individual Files, undated, 1969-1992; Boxes 162-196.
  The working database on the Soviet refuseniks and prisoners of conscience during the Soviet Jewry Movement campaign also included files on émigrés, usually members of families of refuseniks who were allowed to emigrate, and Soviet Jews who were let to leave the Soviet Union as a result of international pressure. Materials in this series were often moved from the refusenik and POC database, as they were allowed by Soviets to emigrate. NCSJ maintained contacts with former Soviet refuseniks and prisoners of conscience, being interested in their fate and in order to organize meetings and events with their participation for raising awareness of the American and Western public about the plight of Soviet Jews and about the successful results of campaign work on behalf of particular Soviet Jews and families.
  The series includes general information and statistics on Soviet Jewish emigration, and on emigration-related issues like the issue of Soviet Jews who left the Soviet Union on the Israeli visas but preferred to resettle in the West (mostly the United States) rather than proceed to Israel. The series is divided into two Subseries: Jewish Émigrés Individual file, undated, 1969-1992 and Subseries B: General information on Jewish émigrés, undated, 1971-1972, 1976-1989.
  - Subseries A: Jewish Émigrés Individual file, undated, 1969-1992; Boxes 162-193.
    - Ab-Ar, undated, 1972-1988 (Box 162)
    - As-Bl, undated, 1974-1988 (Box 163)
    - Bo-Butman, H. [1 of 4], undated, 1974-1988 (Box 164)
    - Butman, H. [2 of 4]-C, undated, 1974-1990 (Box 165)
    - Da-Drag, undated, 1973-1991 (Box 166)
    - Drap-Er, undated, 1974-1992 (Box 167)
    - Es-Fain, undated, 1976 (Box 168)
    - Fainb-Finkelstein, A. with Photo, undated, 1972-1989 (Box 169)
    - Finkelstein, E-Ful, undated, 1974-1992 (Box 170)
    - Fun-Geni with Photos, undated, 1974-1991 (Box 171)
    - Genk-Goldfarb, A. with Photo, undated, 1972-1991 (Box 172)
    - Goldfarb, D. -Godstein, I. [1 of 2], undated, 1973-1987 (Box 173)
    - Godstein, I. [2 of 2] -Gul, undated, 1973-1987 (Box 174)
    - Gur-Kel, undated, 1974-1988 (Box 175)
    - Ker-Kogan, F., undated, 1969-1971, 1974-1988 (Box 176)
    - Kogan, I-Kuznetsov, E. with photo, undated, 1974-1989 (Box 177)
    - Kuznetsov, E-Levich, B., undated, 1973, 1975-1988 (Box 178)
    - Levich, Y.-Lob, undated, 1974-1988 (Box 179)
    - Loi-Mar with Audiocassette, undated, 1971-1973, 1975-1988 (Box 180)
    - Mat-Mende with Photos, undated, 1973-1979 (Box 181)
    - Mendzh-Ol with Photo, undated, 1972, 1975-1988 (Box 182)
    - Or-Po, undated, 1972-1988 (Box 183)
    - Pr-Rubin, V. [1 of 3], undated, 1972-1988 (Box 184)
    - Rubin, V. [2 of 3]-Shkolnik, I. -- Appeals, undated, 1972-1988 (Box 185)
    - Shkolnik, I -- Biographies -- Shtern, M. [3 of 5], undated, 1974-1988 (Box 186)
    - Shtern, M. [4 of 5] -- Sp with Photo, undated, 1972-1988 (Box 187)
    - St-Temkin, A. [1 of 3], 1972-1987 (Box 188)
    - Temkin, A. [2 of 3] -Ts, undated, 1974-1988 (Box 189)
    - Tu-Voli, undated, 1974, 1988 (Box 190)
    - Volv-Yakir, A., undated, 1969-1972, 1974-1987 (Box 191)
    - Yakir, Y-Zalmanson, S., 1971-1987 (Box 192)
    - Zalmanson, V.-Zu with Photos, undated, 1971, 1973-1987 (Box 193)
  - Subseries B: General information on Jewish émigrés, undated, 1971-1972, 1976-1989; Boxes 194-196.
    - Émigrés -- A-L, undated, 1982, 1985-1988 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Émigrés -- M-Z, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Émigrés Conversion, 1982-1983 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Noshrim (Dropouts), 1976, 1979, 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Refugee Act 1980, 1979-1980, 1984 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Refugee Status, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984, 1986-1988 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Refugee Status, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Resettlement of Soviet Jews, 1988-1989 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Russian Emigrants in USA -- Missionaries, 1980-1981 (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Soviet Artists in the U.S., undated, 1980, 1984-1985 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Soviet Emigration Policy and Soviet Jews, 1971-1972, 1976-1977, 1980, 1982-1988 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Soviet Interview Project Paper Series (University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign), 1983-1985 (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Soviet Interview Project Paper Series (University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign), January 1986-March 1986 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Soviet Interview Project Paper Series (University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign), April 1986-May 1986 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Soviet Interview Project Paper Series (University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign), undated, 1987 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Soviet Interview Project, 1979-1980, 1983, 1986 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Jewish Emigration to Israel, 1987, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Soviet Jewish Émigrés -- Relocation -- A-K, 1978-1981 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Jewish Émigrés -- Relocation -- L-Z, 1977-1982 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Temporary Suspension of U.S. Visas, 1988 (Box 196, Folder 7)
- Part 2, Series IX: Jewish Communal and ASJM Organizations Correspondence and Information Materials, undated, 1963-1965, 1971, 1973-1992; Boxes 197-280.
  Arranged into three subseries.
  NCSJ as an umbrella organization placed its work's center of gravity with the local organizations, especially after the adjustment in the middle of 1980s of its policies regarding the local organizations, and that is reflected in the correspondence, memoranda and other documents from this Series. The NCSJ leadership, its New York and Washington offices functioned as a coordinating force and information clearing house to stir up local activism and increase participation of the broader Jewish community. NCSJ heads acted through conducting meetings and consultations with representatives of local communities, through distribution of information on the organization's events and news related to the Soviet Jewry, organization and coordination of visits to the USSR, working out responses to challenges like Presidential administration's resistance to the legislation related to the Most Favored Nation (MFN) status for the USSR and to the issue of "drop outs," Soviet Jewish émigrés reluctant to go to Israel and choosing the US instead.
  NCSJ maintained wide contacts with other American Soviet Jewry Movement organizations, most prominent of which were the UCSJ, ASJ and SSSJ, and with Jewish communal organizations, synagogues and schools, and it is reflected in the documents from this Series. The Series is divided into three Subseries: Subseries A: ASJM-related organization in the U.S., undated, 1963-1965, 1971 1974-1989; Subseries B: UCSJ, undated, 1973-1992; Subseries C: Other ASJM-related organizations, undated, 1977-1991.
  - Subseries A: ASJM-related organization in the U.S., undated, 1963-1965, 1971, 1974-1991; Boxes 197-262.
    - Academic Committee for Soviet Jewry, 1980 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Academic Committee on Soviet Jewry, 1979 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - AKTSIA, 1979, 1981 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Al Tidom Association, 1979-1980 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Alabama, 1978-1979 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Alabama, 1981 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Alabama, 1982-1983 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Alabama, 1985, 1987-1989 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Albany, New York, 1979-1981 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - America-Israel Friendship League, 1984-1985 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, 1982 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), undated, 1985 (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - American Committee on East-West Accords, 1979-1981 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - American Committee on East-West Accords, 1974, 1983-1985 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - American Committee on East-West Accords, January-April 1986 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - American Committee on East-West Accords, undated, May-August 1986 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - American Council for Judaism, 1979 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - American Council of Young Political Leaders, 1979 (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - American Federation of Jewish Fighters, Camp Inmates and Nazi Victims, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - American Federation of Jewish Fighters, Camp Inmates and Nazi Victims, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1974-1976, 1978-1979, 1983, 1989 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - American Gathering of Jewish Holocaust Survivors, 1982-1984 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - American Gathering of Jewish Holocaust Survivors, 1985-1987 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - American Institute of Parliamentarians, 1974-1975 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC), 1978-1981 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC), 1984-1986 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC), 1983-1984 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC), 1982 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1987 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1980 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1981 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1982 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1983 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1984 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1979-1983 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1984-1988 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Congress -- Women's Division, 1979-1980 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - American Jewish Historical Society, 1979-1980 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - American Jewish Historical Society, 1981-1982 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1982-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - American Mizrachi Women, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - American Ort Federation, undated, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - American Zionist Federation, 1979-1981 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - American Zionist Federation, 1982, 1984-1986 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - American Zionist Youth Foundation, 1979, 1981 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - American Zionist Youth Foundation, undated, 1982-1984 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - American Zionist Youth Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - American-Israeli Civil Liberties Coalition, 1982 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Americans for Progressive Israel, 1981 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Americans for Progressive Israel, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Amit Woman, 1986 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Amnesty International, undated, 1979-1981 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Amnesty International, 1981-1987 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1978-1980 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, undated, 1981-1982 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1983 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 1984 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, January-April 1985 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, May-December 1985 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, undated, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith with Poster, "Glasnost has failed" (see also OS1 folder, item I-181A.012), undated, 1987-1989 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Appeal of Conscience Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Appeal of Conscience Foundation, undated, 1984, 1986-1989 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Arizona, 1979 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Arizona, 1980-1981 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Arizona, 1982-1983 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Arizona with Posters (see also OS1 folder, item I-181A.011), 1984 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Arizona, 1985 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Arizona, 1986 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Arizona, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Arkansas, 1982 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1979 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Association of American Publishers, 1978-1981 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Association of American Publishers, 1982 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Association of Invalids and Veterans of World War II, undated, 1976-1979 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Association of Jewish Book Publishers, undated, 1979, 1981-1984 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1982-1983, 1985 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta, GA, 1982-1984 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Atlanta, GA, 1983-1984 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Atlanta, GA, 1985 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Atlanta, GA, undated, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Atlanta, GA, 1987-1989 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Austin, Texas, 1984-1986, 1988 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - B'nai B'rith Academic Consultation, 1982 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - B'nai B'rith Hillel Foundation, undated, 1982-1985 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - B'nai B'rith International, undated, 1979-1981 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - B'nai B'rith International, 1982 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - B'nai B'rith International, 1983-1984 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - B'nai B'rith International, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - B'nai B'rith Women, 1979-1980 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - B'nai B'rith Women, undated, 1984-1986 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - B'nai B'rith Women, undated, 1987-1988 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - B'nai Zion, 1979, 1982, 1984, 1986, 1988 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Baltimore, Maryland, 1979-1980 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Baltimore, Maryland, 1981 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Baltimore, Maryland, 1982 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Baltimore, Maryland, 1983-1986 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Baltimore, Maryland -- 1986 Proposed Conference on Soviet Jewry, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Baltimore, Maryland -- Baltimore Hebrew Congregation Sisterhood, 1983-1984 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Bay Area, California, 1983-1984 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Bibliography Project, 1980-1981 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Boston, MA, 1977-1979 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Boston, Massachusetts, 1981-1982 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Boston, Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Bridgeport, CT, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Brith Sholom, 1982 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Buffalo, New York, 1979-1981 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - California -- Miscellaneous, 1979-1982 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - California, 1982-1983 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - California, 1984-1986 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - California with magazine photo of a demonstration and postcard, 1987 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - California (Freedom Seder for SJ postcard), undated, 1988-1989 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - CATO Institute, 1986 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - CAUSA International, 1983-1984 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Center for Democracy, 1986 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Center for Foreign Policy Options, 1987 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Center for Learning and Leadership, 1987-1988 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1979 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Central Conference of American Rabbis, 1979-1981 (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Central Conference of American Rabbis (CCAR), 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Central Conference of American Rabbis (CCAR), 1984-1987 (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Central Conference of American Rabbis, 1989 (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Chicago, Illinois with Photos, 1982-1984 (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Christian Rescue Effort for the Emancipation of Dissidents (CREED), 1980-1981 (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Christian Rescue Effort for the Emancipation of Dissidents (CREED), 1982 (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Christian Rescue Effort for the Emancipation of Dissidents, 1984-1986 (Box 208, Folder 17)
    - Christian Rescue Effort for the Emancipation of Dissidents, 1987-1988 (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1984 (Box 208, Folder 19)
    - Cincinnati, Ohio, 1982-1984 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Cincinnati, Ohio, 1985-1986 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Citizen Exchange Corps, 1979, 1981 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Citizen Exchange Council, 1984-1987 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - CJF Assembly Members, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Cleveland, OH, 1978-1980 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Cleveland, OH, 1982-1983 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Cleveland, OH, 1984 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Cleveland, OH [1 of 2], 1985 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Cleveland, OH [2 of 2], 1985 (Box 210, Folder 2)